=Dungeon Unlocking=
(Talent hub)
On 22 June 2026,
Tui Games Company
held their usual
monthly themed-party,
(Crazy animal theme party)
crazy animal party.
After the boss, Tui Haowan,
gave his speech,
he announced the start of the party
before leaving.
Six employees sat in a circle
and began sharing urban tales in turn.
This is just the first story.
It was dark.
Suddenly, a severed limb
fell from the ceiling
with the word
(Revenge)
"revenge" written on it.
Don't move.
Don't touch it.
At this time,
the employees,
Ding Staring and Ning Watcha,
recognized it as Tui Haowan's right leg
based on the mosquito coil burn mark.
A strange tale came true.
Conspired to murder and...
Who is the avenger?
We both can.
Why did everyone gradually
show animal attributes
after joining the company?
(Crazy animal theme party)
What is exactly
(The case's detective: Ning Watcha)
behind Tui Games Company?
(The case's detective: Ding Staring)
Door of Truth:
(Jin Goofy)
Chapter Four
(He Struggle. Ke Uh-Oh)
unlocking.
(Nan Shy)
(Case 4: Crazy Animal Theme Party)
(Ding Staring, Ning Watcha, Jin Goofy)
(Nan Shy, He Struggle, Ke Uh-Oh)
(Loading)
(Ning Watcha. Detective. Stamina: 180)
(Profile. Name: Ning Watcha)
(Age: 18. Job: Cleaner)
(Skill Card: Compliment Card)
Awooo.
(Look! The deadly wolf is quite furry)
So aggressive.
(Completely conquered)
So charismatic.
(Lifts his tail to sit)
Wolf King,
(It's too funny)
lifting your tail before you sit?
Am I being emotional? Am I?
No.
(Trying to comfort)
You're completely impartial.
(Refused to hear and see)
Can't hear. Can't see.
Don't scare me.
Capybara.
(Alpha wolf instantly becomes a cub)
(Whatchu looking at?)
(Move aside)
Why did you turn into a pig?
Let's have brave...
(A sudden rap)
b... brave
bravo.
Don't stutter.
He picked up a blade of grass and left.
(Perfect imitation)
We'll go with weapons.
(More confident with weapons)
Let's go.
(Detective starting to put in effort)
Let me reveal the last secret.
(No one tracks down killers like Ning)
Wait. There's a hand.
It proves one thing.
What?
The company's strange tales
we talked about
came true.
So you wrote the note.
So you could be...
(Confidential)
Another reason why it exists
is because we...
(Confidential)
Or my consciousness.
Or maybe I myself...
(Confidential)
If this...
Then Tui Haowan...
(Confidential)
But what is
with these photos?
There's a really terrifying point here.
He has two killing motives now.
(Confidential)
These two appeared at the same time.
It means
the killer used them.
Comparing you two,
your motive is stronger.
(Whose flaw did Ning Watcha catch?)
(Ding Staring.
Detective. Stamina: 1,200)
(Profile. Name: Ning Staring.
Age: 26. Job: Security)
(Skill Card:
Hint Card, Massage Cardx2, Dancing Card)
("Xin"-cited little fox.
Who can withstand Ding?)
You're a fox.
(The real pup is here)
I'm a dog.
You are...
So you two are the detectives.
My apologies.
(Too late)
I only found out now.
So scary.
There's something else.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
This little fox
seems pretty fearless.
Help!
Help.
No. I'll help you hold it.
Reach your hand inside.
It's fine.
It's okay.
(Let me)
I'll reach in.
Why do you speak like that?
He entered my room.
(Staring at you)
Say my name.
(Weapon suppression)
Quickly!
These are... chocolate nails.
(A look from Ding, and all the clues click)
He'll figure it out for you.
Who's this?
He gave it...
(Confidential)
I get it. He has it.
Could this be it?
At the start...
(Confidential)
As his consciousness slowly awakens...
Because he is too nice,
he snapped after hitting rock bottom.
You don't have a motive?
His head actually
looks like...
(Confidential)
So his whole body was...
A little rushed.
He can relate.
It probably wasn't murder.
Do you remember
we saw the severed limb
before entering the cage?
It proves he wasn't...
(Confidential)
when he died.
So he
created the panic himself.
It's like he wants to protect you,
so he...
(Confidential)
and told you.
Well...
(Confidential)
You bought it, didn't you?
(Can Ding identify the killer outright?)
(Jin Goofy. Stamina: 200)
(Profile. Name: Jin Goofy.
Age: 23. Job: HR)
(Skill Card:
Compliment Card. Rewind Card)
(Jing blends in perfectly)
My workplace survival rule is...
If I can't do it,
(Full of emotion)
I'm not doing it.
When trouble comes, avoid it if you can.
If you want to catch me,
I'm too slippery.
(Slippery like a fish)
What a sweet little girl.
(Love at first sight)
I like you.
Aren't you a mermaid?
(Switches instantly)
Oh, right. Why did I turn into a witch?
I was confused.
It's not too late now.
Jin,
if you're being threatened,
just blink.
(Forcing it open)
I'm doing this willingly.
(Jin is surprised)
(Suddenly serious)
Who said
that we were the killers
and wanted to lock us in?
(It's him)
Who? He said that.
Wait.
I'm HR.
The company
forbids office romances.
Say something nice.
(Right on cue)
Capybara, my favorite.
Really?
Yes.
Spill it.
You did it.
(Jin using her brain)
Why
are these...
(Confidential)
You can torment me.
But torment my brother?
I won't allow it.
So you wanted to kill him.
They just think
that you are...
(Confidential)
To be admired.
I want to ask when you found out...
(Confidential)
Did you want to kill the boss?
Was it...
(Confidential)
using same word?
Even a rabbit...
Even a rabbit will bite when cornered.
Wait.
Are you eliminating suspects?
We rule out...
(Confidential)
because he already...
Boss made me
to be on call at all times.
So how could I
wait
until he wasn't around
to sneak into his office...
(Confidential)
Can't figure it out.
(Can Jin Goofy solve the murder?)
(He Struggle. Stamina: 0)
(Profile. Name: He Struggle.
Age: 22. Job: Top motion caption actor)
(Skill Card: Item Card, Copy Card,
Free Card, Singing Card, Freeze Card)
(Capybara mood barely "Ling"ers)
Because I'm like a capybara.
So when I think back on it,
it felt fine.
That's right.
I just brush it off.
(Completely unfazed)
(Cool as a cucumber)
(Stay calm, and things will go well)
(Why struggle?)
(Brain has shut down)
(Softly roasting)
Your ears are sticking up again.
My ears?
I ate them myself.
(Soft but fierce)
Don't press me. Don't.
(Presses anyway)
You have never
(Front-row spectator)
danced this for me.
(Chews)
(Small and helpless)
Look.
(Watch closely)
(It's yours)
(Electric shock)
Get something.
A tool.
(Fishing an invisible fish)
(Play bug never goes away)
Do I look like I'd dare?
(Thoughts stay clear. The fog vanishes)
I have taken off
my capybara coat.
There's no framing anyone here.
This should be connected...
(Confidential)
That connects.
Because he tortured your beloved...
(Confidential)
So you want to kill your boss.
Although
we both
are full of resentment,
our personalities...
Remember this.
One's a capybara.
One's an introvert.
After squeezing every last bit of value,
that person has
to be killed.
If you dare,
split your votes between the two of us.
I didn't realized I was suffering.
I wanted to kill boss,
but I didn't dare.
Then did you
realized then
when talking with Mr. Tui?
But it says here...
(Confidential)
You've overlooking these words.
Then...
(Confidential)
Could the killer have taken it?
I'm thinking if we can rule him out.
(Who did He Struggle rule out?)
(Ke Uh-Oh. Stamina: 0)
(Profile. Name: Ke Uh-Oh. Age: 22)
(Job: Official cosplayer and sales.
Skill Card: Rewind Card)
(An obedient adorable puppy)
I'm the puppy-type employee.
That's me.
Are you a puppy?
Yes.
Sniff.
(Obeys without question)
Okay. Now go.
Lead the way.
Where is he?
Jin,
(Who could resist this?)
you've never danced this for me.
(So cared)
(What should I do?)
Huggy!
Hugs.
Sorry.
Again.
Once more time.
(Not satisfied)
Again?
Are you really going to catch it?
(Skill achieved)
(Showing off a fierce side)
You read it, bro.
You give it more emotion.
No.
Okay.
I want you
to use that puppy-life feeling.
(Can't do puppy at all)
Wait.
Come on. What are you waiting for?
Just do it already.
It's your fault.
Now, we can start
tearing into each other.
(Ke is very suspicious)
There are many ways to solve
a problem,
why must it be murder?
One day, I noticed
sometimes
when I reach my hand into the hole,
there'd be another hand inside.
I later realized something was off.
Because...
it happened far too often.
So we are...
(Confidential)
(Begins searching everyone)
Wait.
Friends.
This was pulled by the killer
during the crime.
But how were we all here?
I got it.
So when he...
(Confidential)
At that time,
a different personality emerges.
I think
that's a convincing theory.
We have to assume the killer
can access...
That's not it.
The two people he found...
(Confidential)
So he can't be ruled out.
We can't eliminate suspects
based on this.
That's good.
We know how the murder happened.
You and...
(Confidential)
Did you two have some sort
of plan together?
I actually think we can rule him out.
(Can Ke Uh-Oh find the key
to identifying the killer?)
(Nan Shy. Profile. Name: Nan Shy)
(Age: 22. Job: Game designer)
(Skill Card: Summon Card)
Hi.
(Cute bunny welcomes you with open arms)
Do I have to dance?
Yes. Together.
Dance, everyone.
Who is the soft one?
(Without hesitation)
Me. I'm the soft one.
(Cute)
(Nan is very shy)
(Cute but fearless)
It's alright.
One foot.
(Seen plenty of big scenes)
Should I pick it up?
(Curiosity at max)
(Acts right at home)
Oh, I can't look yet?
You're so curious.
(Scouting the area)
Scan first to hide better later.
No!
(Comforting)
Don't be scared.
It wasn't me.
Don't ruin our relationship.
I don't want that.
I found the key.
No. Don't make things up.
(Adventurous bunny)
It's open.
She's so brave.
(Best emotional support)
You did well, Jin Goofy.
I miss you.
Me too!
There was a huge speaker.
You!
(Cuts straight to the point)
You've been acting the whole time.
This is a setup.
It wasn't me.
Boss
actually knew
you were becoming a capybara.
He was actually...
(Confidential)
No. I want to get him out
but realized we can't leave.
(Cuts straight to the point)
I hadn't joined on 21 April.
Because you're an introvert.
You're socially anxious.
But he forced you to livestream.
That made you even more miserable.
He must've been shining a flash
in his face the whole time.
So his limbs were cut off with a saw.
That...
(Confidential)
Wasn't one of them burned?
But you wrote that word, didn't you?
The killer wanted to get out,
so they made us enter first.
You did it all for Jin?
He has no way
to explain himself anymore.
(Who did Nan lock in on?)
(Dungeon Bonus Station)
(Dungeon Bonus Station Rules)
(Dungeon Bonus Station regularly
refreshes limited challenge tasks!)
(Complete each episode's goal
to activate surprise little perks!)
(Come refresh your buff library!)
(The Truth 2026)
Welcome to Dungeon Bonus Station.
(Pretend to know what to draw challenge)
Players need to draw
based on two unusual
creature names given
according to their imagination
or understanding.
While drawing,
they need to quickly answer
the director's questions
After finishing,
they need to compare their drawings
with the actual photos.
If it looks similar
and the explanation is reasonable,
they succeed.
Bring it on.
The first animal is barn owl.
(First creature name: Barn owl)
Barn owl.
Okay.
Naked sea angel.
(Second creature name: Naked sea angel)
Naked as in exposed.
Okay.
Challenge begins now.
(Challenge begins)
Among this season's players,
who do you think is the easiest to fool?
(Let me think)
Among the players,
who's the easiest to fool?
Me.
(Answering while drawing)
No. I'm joking.
It's Jin.
Jin might currently...
(Taking shape)
Compared to us,
she has fewer Golden Keys.
(Bro, stop talking)
Who do you think is
the strongest physically?
Strongest physically.
That would be He and that guy,
Ke.
(Physical strength representatives)
They both
are very strong.
(Among the season's players)
Who plays the killer the best?
(Need to think carefully)
Plays the best killer.
I think...
(Electro Kid duo)
He and Ding are pretty good.
Because they both
are not obvious.
That's impressive.
(Compliment mode activated)
If the detective team is a family,
which family member
would you want to be?
I'd be the family chef.
(Thoughtful Chef Ning is here)
I can cook for them.
(Adding details)
Who do you think
(Throughout the season's performance)
changed the most?
Changed the most.
I think it's Ke.
In this season,
he took on more responsibility.
(Became more reliable)
It's great.
Even I sometimes
(Starting to rely on him)
really depend on him.
When it comes to solving cases,
he's also
very smart.
(Barn owl completed)
Which outfit did you like
the most?
Probably the ancient costume.
Because it's been
more than two years
since I...
last filmed an ancient drama.
So when I wore it again,
for a moment,
it felt like I returned
to filming again.
There are many memories.
(Full of nostalgia)
Use one word
to predict today's performance.
I can't predict
because this season's script settings
are very...
How should I put it?
Unusual.
Exceeded my expectations.
(Almost finished)
And the plots
are also very complicated.
I don't know
and can't predict my performance.
But I do hope
(A small wish)
that I can identify the killer.
Alright.
(Done drawing)
Show us your barn owl
and naked sea angel.
Barn owl.
Aren't I amazing?
I drew Sun Wukong's face.
Then an eagle's beak
with an eagle’s body.
So yeah.
This is a barn owl.
It's exactly the same, right?
(Very similar barn owl)
A monkey face.
Yes.
You drew it spot on.
Yeah.
Because I think I've seen it before.
(Knowledgeable)
What about the naked sea angel?
I think I know it.
(The naked sea angel in his memory)
It's like
a sea creature
that looks like a butterfly.
Very tiny.
Looks like a butterfly.
But
since it lives in the sea,
so I gave it a fish tail.
Naked sea angel.
(The real naked sea angel)
(Naked sea angel)
Look at it.
(A pelagic molluscs
from the sea angel family)
(Hermaphroditic with a translucent body)
Explain it.
Isn't it?
Look.
Even the tentacles are the same.
(Not letting of any detail)
And the wings
went through some artistic processing
(Added his own design)
and the whole thing
got some extra patterns.
I think there are many varieties
(Brand-new species)
of sea angels.
The main body structure.
This part
is very similar.
It's practically identical.
And the tail.
I added some
European art-style
imagination.
(Brain overheating)
Like Fauvism.
(Just added some decor)
It's very bold.
So everyone
can learn about sea angel
(Comparison helps deepen impression)
through such a bizarre artwork.
This is calling on us
(We should all protect marine life)
the need to protect marine ecosystem.
Right?
It also serves
an environmental protection purpose.
Okay.
(Liu Yuning challenge successful)
Are you ready?
Yes.
Please begin your challenge.
Okay.
Barn owl.
(Barn owl and blue-footed booby)
Blue-footed booby.
(Begins drawing)
Among the season's players,
who do you think is the Iron Tank?
I think Zhang Linghe and Zhou Keyu
both became the Iron Tank.
(Double tank bodyguards)
(Among this season's players)
Who is the easiest to fool?
Among the season's players,
I think the easiest to fool
(Innocent little bunny)
is Miss Zhang Ruonan.
Among the season's players,
who is the cutest?
I think Ding is the cutest.
(Cutest)
Who gets jealous the most?
(Simple sketch style)
I think it's Zhang Linghe.
Jealous of who?
Of everyone.
(Jealous prince)
He's jealous if you don't give him attention.
because he...
You're done?
Yeah.
(Finished quickly)
Alright.
Let's see.
It's similar.
Very.
(Barn owl and blue-footed booby
extremely similar)
Why is it so similar?
It's like I've seen the answer before.
(So similar. No explanation needed)
(Blue-footed booby)
(Jin Jing challenge successful)
A creature called sand dollar.
(First creature name: Sand dollar)
Is it a creature?
Yes.
(Very confused)
It is.
Use your imagination.
You draw,
and I'll ask you questions.
(Starts imagining)
Among all the players,
who's the easiest to fool?
Easiest to fool...
Ding, I guess.
(Easiest to fool)
Because he's the kindest.
(Among the season's players)
Who is the Iron Tank?
(Recognized tank)
Iron Tank. Zhou Keyu.
(Among the season's players)
Who is the mood-maker?
Mood-maker...
(Mood-maker)
Jin.
(Multi-tasking)
(Among the season's players)
Who's the foodie?
Foodie. Me.
(Certified by himself)
Among the players,
if you had to pick someone
to add more spice,
who would you pick?
Ding.
(Special affection from He)
Which outfit do you like the most?
The white long trench coat.
(He's favorite)
Alright.
(Done drawing)
You're done with the first?
Yes.
Describe your drawing first.
Sand dollar.
(Reptile. Sand)
It's a reptile on sand.
(He's pun. Sand and money)
And it's covered in money.
Sand dollar.
(Making the logic work)
Let me show you.
(Sand dollar. Common name for Clypeasteroida)
Do you think it's similar?
(Searching for similarities)
I think it does.
(Let me explain)
Because what I drew is this.
What is the frame outside?
That is
(I think fast)
another background element.
A decoration.
It's part of my concept.
(Logical enough)
(Second creature name: Barn owl)
Second. Barn owl.
Among the players,
who has the biggest contrast?
Biggest contrast...
(Biggest contrast)
Ding.
When I first met him,
he was handsome.
But he's actually
(Cute)
a very cute kid.
If the detective team is a family,
which family member would you be?
I want to be everyone's sibling.
(Not asking for much)
Yeah. We're all siblings.
The same generation.
(Invitation to be in the same gen)
What kind would you
recommend everyone try?
Freshwater seafood.
We're near Taihu Lake.
It's been sometime since I ate it.
(A true foodie)
I'm done drawing.
Let's see.
(Revealing his masterpiece)
I don't know what a barn owl looks like.
(Real barn owl)
It runs?
(Confused)
Can't it fly?
Why is it called an owl?
This...
(Searching for similarities)
Alright.
(The world is weird)
It looks strange.
Actually, my drawing is pretty similar.
(Saying it confidently)
First of all,
they look very abstract.
Everyone can see that.
What I draw
was its hands.
It's just
(Type 1 if you think it looks similar)
my drawing has better proportions.
(Golden ratio)
Its hands are longer.
This barn owl's hands are shorter.
(Rude, much?)
But it's the same species.
Everyone can tell at a glance.
Right?
(Who will speak for the owl?)
Fine, you pass.
(Zhang Linghe challenge successful)
Okay. What creature?
The first one is sand dollar.
(First creature name: Sand dollar)
Sand dollar?
Yes.
(Trying to decipher it)
Sand dollar?
Sand on the beach.
Dollar?
Money dollar.
Money dollar?
Okay.
The second is sea angel.
I can start drawing, right?
Yes.
We'll start the questions.
(Among the season's players)
Who is the easiest to fool?
Nan Shy.
Among the players,
who is the most timid?
The easiest to scare.
Most timid.
Jin Goofy.
Among the players,
(Drawing seriously)
Who plays the murderer the best?
Me.
(Top murderer)
(Among the season's players)
who has the biggest contrast?
Biggest contrast?
Ding.
(Certified by the fox)
If you were doing a solo quest,
who would you want to do it with?
Myself.
(Brave Ding fears so challenge)
(Trying not to laugh)
Throughout the whole season,
who do you think changed the most?
Throughout the season?
(Desensitized growth)
Probably me.
(Done drawing)
Alright.
Show it to the camera.
Okay. This is sand dollar.
(Sand dollar)
It is an animal.
Never heard of it.
This is a fish?
I'm pretty accurate.
(Begin explaining his art)
Firstly, it looks like a human body.
Isn't it?
(Breaking it down)
It has a head and hands.
And this is the body.
And the legs.
(Clean lines)
And it has all these lines.
So I think it looks especially similar.
(Convincing explanation)
Sea angel.
And the sand dollar.
First of all,
it also looks very much alike.
Sand
and a pattern in the middle.
And some tentacles.
One more thing.
I used sand.
Look. The small dots.
(Explaining the similar details)
Looks like a coin.
So it's called a sand dollar.
Okay.
(Ding Chengxin challenge successful)
Ready?
Yes.
Please begin.
Barn owl.
(Tough opening)
(Among the season's players)
Who is the easiest to fool?
Among the players, I think...
I should be the easiest one to fool.
(Among the season's players)
(Who do you think) is the most timid?
The most timid is probably Jin.
Among the players,
who is the most reliable?
(Steady and reassuring)
The most reliable should be Ning.
Among the players,
(Bold drawing style)
Who played the killer the best?
I think Ning and He are quite good.
Jin is amazing too.
(Ke's full approval)
Among the season's players,
who is the best at deduction?
Best at deduction must be Ning.
No doubt.
Among the season's players,
who is the most caring?
Most caring person.
I think it's...
Actually, everyone
takes care of each other.
(A loving big family)
Among this season's players,
(Drawing complete)
(Who) has the biggest contrast?
The biggest contrast?
I think it's Jin.
When she is the killer,
her state is always
very peace...
hard to figure her out.
Yeah.
Explain
your drawing process.
Barn owl.
(Completely exhausted)
I really have no idea.
Dude.
I don't know how to draw this
Barn owl?
But the characteristics of an eagle,
I did make it obvious.
(The owl in Ke's eyes)
Firstly,
look at this.
(An owl's eyes)
The line. The eyes show.
Its vision is 1,000 km.
The height is 10,000 meters.
(Flying high)
It flies at 10,000 meters.
An owl's vision
that can see 1,000 km.
That's all I can do.
I've done what I can.
I'll give you a picture of an owl.
Tell me if you think it looks similar.
If it does, and your explanation
is reasonable, you pass.
Okay.
I think...
I think there are some similarities.
(Can't hold it in)
What is a barn owl?
Does this creature really exist?
Friends.
(Yes. It does)
Everyone watching at home.
(Seeking answers online)
Does this really exist?
A barn owl.
Barn...
And it's running on the ground.
(Ground-running owl)
It's an owl running on the ground.
Friends.
(Bro, I support you)
This owl is running.
(Back to the topic)
But this is my logic.
(Ke's drawing summary)
You will see
a lot of the things I draw,
the information I give
is enough for you
to identify the species.
or example, flying at 10,000 meters.
Right?
The thousand-kilometer
owl vision.
Right?
So I think in general
I still provided
the information everyone needed.
How would you rate the similarity?
he similarity... I would say
out of 100,
(Screenshot this. It'll be tested)
it is about 60.
(A passing grade)
It definitely passes.
Yeah.
Right.
(Feeling guilty)
No problem.
Yup.
One more chance.
Hang on.
Something simpler.
(Turning red)
This, my friends.
well.
We are just...
Yeah.
(Requesting a rewind card)
Okay.
Don't let anyone else see this.
(Limited edition)
Alright. Next question.
Next question.
Ready?
Sand dollar.
What?
(Let's speak Chinese)
"Sha" from sand and "qian" from money.
Sand dollar?
It is an animal?
Yes.
Sand dollar?
(Call for help)
Save me!
This is super easy.
Friends.
(Accepting reality in 0 seconds)
Among this season's players,
who do you want to add some spice to?
Of course it's Ding.
I'd give it to him.
(I'm your best bud)
Add lots of spice.
Among this season's players,
who would you most like
to be a detective with?
I want to be a detective
with Ning the most
because he is amazing
(Great at deduction)
at deducting.
Among this season's players,
who do you think is a foodie?
Foodie?
(Instantly decides the game)
I think it's definitely He.
Yeah.
Which outfit do you like the most?
Which outfit?
I'm done drawing.
Which outfit this season...
The one I like more is...
(Ke's favorite)
the time we were the Longdong Army.
Okay.
This one shouldn't be a problem,
right?
(Very confident)
This is
(Sun, money, beach, waves)
sand dollar.
Coin
and lots of sand.
Yup.
Please collect your sand dollar.
Okay.
Okay, friends.
Alright.
I'll be honest.
This deserves an 80.
(No 6XX drawing style)
The shape and every aspect
(But I have Ke's mouth)
are very similar.
Friends watching at home,
I believe
the audience's eyes are sharp.
They will give me
(If you think it looks alike, comment 6)
the fairest judgement.
Right?
Look.
The circle is correct first of all.
Secondly, I even drew
the lines around it.
(Need to observe carefully)
I gave very subtle hints.
It doesn't have much
distinguishing detail.
(Ke's innovation)
I could have drawn another circle
or drawn a star in the middle.
You might even think it was a flower
if it was drawn on top,
right?
So it's obvious.
I can get a 90.
(His mouth deserves a thumbs-up)
Right, it's absolutely spot on.
Okay.
You win.
(Zhou Keyu challenge successful)
Challenge successful.
Are you ready?
Please start.
Barn owl.
Barn owl?
(Brain continuously searching)
I have absolutely no idea
how to draw this.
(Search fail)
Among the season's players,
who is the easiest to fool?
That would be me.
(Same wavelength)
Nan Shy.
It's my first time playing this game.
Newbie asking for guidance)
I haven't gotten the hang of it.
Before coming,
who did you think was the most timid?
I think Jin.
Hmm.
Because?
Because I just feel like
she's not very brave.
(Already stopped drawing)
Are you done drawing?
Yes.
So quick.
Show everyone
what you drew.
You can see what the real barn owl
looks like.
Alright.
It is indeed a barn owl.
How do you think you drew it?
I think...
Look.
The heart shape is drawn the same.
(Same heart-shaped face)
Yes.
Right.
It's the same.
They are exactly the same.
(Nan is very satisfied)
Even the eyes are the same.
The nose is missing.
I'll draw a nose for it now.
(Emergency modification)
Then you can draw the second one.
Okay.
Sea angel.
(What even is that?)
What?
Sea angel.
It's also called a sea butterfly.
(Weak and helpless)
During the show,
who do you think is
the best at deduction?
I think everyone in the detective team
is probably suited for deduction.
(Everyone is an expert)
Among this season's players,
who do you think is the Iron Tank?
Anyway, I think Jin Jing
definitely isn't one
because I know she's quite timid.
(Rules Jin out first)
As for the others,
they could all be the Iron Tank.
Yeah.
Recommend one friend to join The Truth.
Who will you pick?
My newly friend, Meng.
(Meng Ziyi)
Have you finished drawing?
I finished long ago.
(Waiting quietly to reveal the drawing)
Alright, let's reveal it now.
It can't be said to be exactly the same,
but it actually is.
Alright.
(Zhang Ruonan's challenge successful)
Congratulations, you won.
(Everyone succeeded)
(Bonus Station updated.
Rewards distributed)
(Snack Boost)
(Utility Boost)
(Squishy Boost)
Alright. For the Dungeon Bonus Station,
there is a double surprise.
Please pick two out of the three cards.
Alright.
I'll choose gummies
and chocolates.
(Liu Yuning picked Heart Gummies)
Everyone might...
Because sometimes when using your brain,
you need a lot of energy and calories.
So let them replenish some sugar.
Of course I'd pick Snack Boost.
(Jin Jing's pick)
I want the Fruit Bowl
and Calm Banana.
(Zhang Linghe's pick)
Ice-cold drink
(Must try the new menu)
and Soft bun.
I get both food and drinks.
(Smart foodie)
I want the bread
(Ding Chengxin picked soft bun)
and Choco-incidence.
(and Choco-incidence)
(Zhou Keyu picked Crispy Meat Bites)
Firstly, Crispy Meat Bites is a must.
(and soft bun)
Bun.
This is a pair,
everyone.
Then I'll choose Guess Who.
(Zhang Ruonan chooses Guess who)
I can choose food too, right?
Yes.
I want to try Sour Q Candy.
(Sour Q Candy)
(Liu Yuning: Heart Gummies & Choco-incidence.
Jin Jing: Fruit Bowl & Calm Banana. Zhang Linghe: Ice-cold Drink & Soft Bun)
(Ding Chengxin: Choco-incidence & Soft Bun.
Zhang Ruonan: Guess Who & Sour Q Candy. Zhou Keyu: Crispy Meat Bites & Soft Bun)
(Rewards have been delivered)
There are some snacks here.
Have some water.
I'll pour it.
Your hand is hurt.
Let me.
(Super thoughtful)
Here.
You drink it.
You.
There's more.
Thank you.
Capybara.
Hepybara.
There are so many
(Discovers Ke's snack stash)
of your snacks here.
Dried fruit.
Is this chocolate?
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(Viewing Calendar)
♪Come now, players all,
let the game of reason start♪
♪Unlock each hidden trial,
let courage spark the dark♪
♪Night falls slow, shadows grow,
the sleuth is lost inside the maze♪
♪Figures pass, lanterns sparse,
dark currents drift without a trace♪
♪Wind picks up, footsteps rush,
cold laughter swallowed by the dark♪
♪Truth concealed, the night
stands still, and nothing leaves a mark♪
♪An unsigned letter, coded words,
the solvers gather one by one♪
♪A broken game, illusion reigns,
who's hiding what they've done?♪
♪Hushed voices, nerves on edge,
wrapped in smoke and mirrors still♪
♪The next second, deeper riddles,
or the answer to the kill♪
♪Every piece of truth
has finally come to light♪
♪Unlock the mystery, turn the question,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Side by side, no holding back,
follow every clue to find the truth♪
♪The story blurs like flowers in fog,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Search for the vanished cipher,
trace the proof, and face the sleuth♪